can I expand on that sure can I expand
on that yeah I would
say be
careful on what you're scared
of that's
deep
law attraction baby yeah yeah for sure
uh that was good so Sandra what would
you tell your five-year-old self
to keep loving and keep wearing my heart
on my sleeve don't ever change
that
um leou what is one thing that you would
would change from your past if you had
one thing to change what would what
would that
be if I could change it yeah one part
because everyone will say oh I can't I
don't want to change anything but
there's some things I would change that
would be I change zeros in my bank
account when I was younger you I would
say I would say um save more
money s save way more money oh
jeez I know it's lightning round but
what would I
change I have an idea
[Laughter]
all eyes on
me all eyes on me I would have done this
RV thing sooner
prach can I get an amen from the
congregation yes she said to get in the
RV on the hustle Zone I need to get some
organs in here man I got to get some for
real oh yeah
but
Hallelujah
uh in the
future what Legacy do you want to set
aside for your
kids go
first I want them to be able to do
whatever they
want like as far as who they want to be
who they want to become you know what
extracurricular activities they want to
take part
in I want I want them to be able to to
have those experiences because through
our
experiences is how we grow into an adult
and and and and just pass on all our
love and and all that to
people Sandra so Legacy M Legacy as far
as like how he answered it or Legacy as
far as just the future what would you
want to leave for your kids like what
kind of Legacy what what would you leave
behind for people to know about
you man just like that's hard one that
is a hard one like how to have always
have that adventurous
spirit and not to follow the crowd to
really follow their their intuition and
and understand that it's all about it
all stems from selflove I really want
them to love themselves so much that it
just pouring out onto other people
because I think that's kind of what
happened in my case oops sorry I think
that's kind of what happened in my case
was I I was so full of love from all the
love I received and so I want to keep
passing that and I want them to keep
passing that that way it could pour on
to people like I was able to pour on to
him awesome now uh so folks we're going
to conclude the night uh thank thank you
guys for for coming in sharing your
stories I don't know this if this was
what you expected from the hustle Zone
but what did you guys like the did you
guys like the
experience absolutely awesome yes we
love we love the hustle Zone and Bs High
created man I mean you you've made a
brilliant Exquisite platform for him I
mean that's why I've enjoyed you when I
when when I first friend requested you
you know I was like wow this guy's onest
something he has you know extremely uh
uh sharp Vision like you he
knows he knows where his brand is going
guys you know what I mean and and when
you get behind someone that has that
vision and they do not give up that's a
winner you know that you could bet on
him every single day you know and that's
why I got behind Ryan Perez I mean he
he's if you talk to this guy on the
phone man you will understand he knows
what the he's talking about man you know
you
know on Facebook yeah
[Music]
and we're live
what's going on folks welcome to the
hustle Zone yesterday uh oh sorry it was
uh November 18th the first episode of
The Hustle Zone um and I believe Stacy
AC cross uh was one of the first people
to be on the show to have an official
interview um we had another person on
there but I wish not to name that
person's name so we're going to say that
Stacy across was the first person there
you go but um I
um I am so happy
because this is kind of bittersweet
because when I did Stacy a cross's
first um when I did this first when I
did that first show um we had a lot of
people that came on to that show and one
gentleman that came on to this show is
our guest tonight um uh and he was he
was all up in the comments he was like
agreeing with what I was what what was
being said
and um and then he immediately added me
as a friend and then you know um and
then I'll tell you the story of how we
kind of got talking um afterwards but I
am super duper excited for um um our
guests tonight so it's not just him but
with his wife and um we recently
collaborated on a production uh and uh
it it was super awesome because that
production got over 6,000 views so I'm
talking money you know I mean like this
is crazy uh but um before we get into
the hustle Zone um folks again it's been
a year since we've been doing these
interviews so big shout out to the
hustle Zone I mean we started off um
this is a over a year and a half project
started off with Shane the train you
know and kind of migrated into this
beautiful show that is now the first the
world's first living
documentary in the world right you go on
to our website and then you're going to
see clips of entrepreneurs talking about
their story now what makes the hustle
zone different is that we expand on
their lives as opposed to talking about
you know the basic stuff like so what do
you think about the entrepreneurial
mindset you know like I'm not really
into all that stuff I I don't really
like that stuff because I think some
people talk about Karma and they're
Christian you know karma is Hindu and
people are talking about Karma and they
don't know what they're talking about
you know we we we want to get rid of all
that nonsense that [ __ ] and really
talk about the heart of what makes
people tick and you know and that's why
this this this this this platform this
brand has done so well and it took me a
year I said last year I was going to do
a magazine which kind of turned into the
living documentary now you guys can go
to hustlez own.tv and see all of that
and you guys can also become guests if
you guys go to our page click on the
hustle zone or the living documentary uh
contributors you'll be able to sign up
and be a guest on the show and we also
have topics like you know are you and I
I have to say are you in the sex
industry we want to talk to you are you
did you come into money um through uh uh
through your parents
um did you were you rich and then became
poor we want all those stories um so
that we can add it to this uh to this
documentary and lastly uh the whole
point of this this this this project is
so that my
son and our guest children can look at
this later on and say Hey I want to be
an
entrepreneur because they hear the
stories they hear the grit the grind
that goes behind it so you know either
way I'm so happy that we're here it's
actually you know what I mean when you
think about it it's emotional because
it's like when I was doing this this was
during the time when you know business
was kind of slow I wasn't shaved I was
like um I Would Do the Hustle Zone just
to clear my mind and just to get you my
frustrations out and just to remind
myself that I'm not going to quit and
then a year later you know all of this
stuff has is is happening so I'm super
happy for for our guest tonight so uh I
want to I want you guys to give a big
shout out to uh lwis class and Sandra
Crespo uh how are you guys doing tonight
hold on one second let me just CU you
guys in what's going on
folks and we're
live so I mean you guys are you you you
guys are probably my you guys are my
favorite people can you scoot over a
little bit uh yeah oh the other way the
other
way you guys are my favorite my favorite
people because you know your story just
is is amazing and we're going to get
into that um in a second but I I watch
your stuff um I love all the trips that
you go on um you're doing a lot of
things that a lot of people wish to do
and um you know and I'm I'm I'm so happy
that we can share the stage and finally
have this this conversation but uh but
how are you guys doing like how how how
how are things never less than out
standing my brother awesome we are doing
amazing yeah life is good right now um
hasn't always been this
way but like you said we have been able
to do um all of our adventures and share
them with the world really we share our
lives through the power video and
hopefully
will inspire Millions to find their
definition of freedom just like we have
awesome and I want to just you know of
course I got a shout out to all the
people that are in the hustle Zone
tonight so we got Orlando in there he's
asking what software I use hit me up
Orlando I have Bai creative.com where we
do these live streams um um we're we're
getting into live stream marketing so if
you guys are interested in starting your
own show we would love to produce your
show uh we have Patrick Voss in the
house we just did a amazing video with
Patrick Voss what's going on uh uh Mike
wimbish uh good evening and uh we got
Adrian ande we got Mark uh we have Rob
we have we have all kinds of people in
here tonight so thank you guys all for
tuning in and so I'm going to start it
off like we have a tradition we have a
very specific set of questions we ask
every single show and the first question
my fans would not be happy if I didn't
ask this question but what is your story
now I'm going to ask um you know before
you met now I want I'm going to start
off with you uh Sandra and then we'll
we'll we'll go uh to Lewis but tell us
before you met like what was your story
how did you grow
up okay so me I I love I love love going
far this far back because I think that
sometimes we don't share this enough but
me I actually grew up in a very stable
house which is actually very rare I feel
like nowadays um completely stable you
know I always had my mom and my dad
there and we vacationed a lot which
probably you know which goes more into
now how I live and they literally um
made it a point they were extremely hard
workers they made it a point to always
take us on vacation three to four times
a year my brother and I um they always
worked very very hard I grew up my whole
life watching them work we grew up in
New York City and the hustle and bustle
of it all and I just saw them working
very hard their whole life and me I was
a very very big entrepreneur and I
didn't really get that from either one
of them I I got that from my mom's side
of the family my grandmother my aunt and
so I was the child that like my mom
would be like oh my God where did this
kid come from I was like creating things
to sell at school or on the corner I
would create little greeting cards and I
was so young like this was me growing up
and my mom would be like where where's
these ideas coming from Sandra you know
she' get embarrassed um but she would
not she would always make me feel like I
could do whatever I wanted to do she
always knew that she was like oh well
you know so I grew up my whole life with
a lot of support I was very confident I
was very um introverted but thanks to
certain things that my mom did like I
don't think she realized it until you
know I I became an adult and I told her
like she would stick me in everything
and anything possible like she had me in
basketball she had me in swimming she
had me in dance classes like she didn't
want me to get into trouble so she would
put me into all of these things to keep
me busy so thanks to that I was able to
not be so socially awkward I think um
which I thank her for because I think I
would have been because I was very
introverted like I always needed energy
to recoup and so um after 15 years of
living in New York City they decided to
bring us to the Poconos actually which
is where we're currently at which is so
surreal to me but that's another story
and we um lived here because they wanted
to get us out of the city so I we I was
here for five years and then I ended up
in Florida
which is where I met Louis and so I had
a very stable environment um my parents
unfortunately things did not work out
for them but by then I was already an
adult and you know by then I was
understanding they did a lot of sacrific
for us growing up and I think that was a
big part of of what made me of who I am
today so Louis likes to say that I grew
up with rainbows and butterflies in my
head and I and I really think I did and
it was really thanks to them and I love
them and I thank them for that and I
know that that's not that's a more of a
rare case I think more people live um
more like ls's story that's like harder
and the tough stuff and and I can't even
say I tell him sometimes my story is
kind of
boring and um and then and Lewis what
what what what what's your
story the total
opposite to be quite frankly um so uh
where do I start okay so I was born in
New Jersey all right um my dad you know
pretty much always did whatever he could
for work and stuff like that um for a
little while we were in a um apartment
building in New Jersey which he was the
um what do they call
superintendent and long story short with
that I burnt down the the apartment I
burned it down we were we had a baby
sitter and she wasn't really paying
attention to us and me being like two
years old I found a lighter I was
playing with a lighter boom caught the
couch on fire and we lost everything
like my dad didn't have anything left I
mean not even pictures I don't have baby
pictures or any of that stuff because of
that fire so then um my dad end up
hooking up with this lady her name was
Katie Katie she was a Bell's bondsman
Bell's bonds woman I'm sorry I hate to
interrupt you in the middle of your
story but you forgot one of the biggest
things what's that your
mom oh yeah okay so the reason why my
dad was a superintendent in the building
and um he went with this other woman is
because my mother was actually caught
cheating on my dad in New York while
lived in New York for a brief time in
the Bronx and um my dad was like F this
I'm going to leave and I actually still
remember it's ingrained in my brain that
you know my mom and dad was having a
tug-of-war in the middle of the street
with uh my brother and I you know and um
so then after that my dad had met this
woman and she was a Bell's bonds
lady and we went to Florida and you know
my dad pretty much strug red his whole
life he's a hard freaking worker man
like my dad is one of the hardest
workers I know still to this day he's in
his 50s he's a plumber he bust his ass
every single day and I got my my work
ethic I got from my pops like 100% my
big heart I got for my pops you know but
growing up it was just me my dad and my
brother for a long time you know um his
relationship with Katie didn't work out
for very long it was a few years we when
we came to Florida and then um my dad
after that would just go through
relationship and relationship and I
never quite knew exactly what love was
from a woman because I I just didn't
feel that from any woman I never felt
that ever before in my whole life so you
know we go through all these
relationships and and I I just grew up
in this home where it's not very stable
um you know we had all kind of issues I
mean we've had our house broken into
from my dad's friends and basically I
was not in the best environment like
that's why like we strive so hard to
live the way we live because that is
important to us like we know how you
know how important your environment is
anyway when you're coming up I mean just
listen to Sandra's story you know
everything was butterflies and rainbows
to her because of how her parents
brought her up you know and I pretty
much didn't have that in my um pretty
much have that in my life but from a
young age you know I always I was always
like on on an entrepreneur mindset like
I always wanted to own my own business I
always wanted to you know do my own
thing I I any job I ever had it didn't
last very long because I just don't like
Authority I don't like you know people
trying to make me a cookie cutter figure
and that's all across the board it
doesn't matter you know where you put me
at
but you know when when I finally met
Sandra I think is the first time I could
really say that I ever learned how to
love a woman and and and felt actually
what that love like that love actually
was you know I never I never experienced
that before I mean holy crap I had so
many rough relationships before Sandra
and um I'm just glad I met
her that's awesome uh so I'm I'm G to
ask you Sandra you know
and yeah it sounds like butterflies and
and you know it sounds like unicorns and
rainbows but you know being I'm an
introvert myself and I I I found life
really challenging and uh especially
when you saw people just acting in a
certain way and you know you internalize
a lot of things and uh you know
especially you have friends that kind of
want to do bad things Etc you're kind of
internalizing it and not wanting to
speak up or or or say anything
did you ever have a problem with that
being cuz you you seem to be in a you
had you had a special environment your
parents um raised you to be you know
exceptional however not every kid and
everyone that you surround yourself what
would have been cut from that same cloth
so how did you fit in when you were a
kid how did you kind of learn to to find
that confidence in in your gifts that
you that were bestowed upon you uh
through your
parents oh that's a good
question I think that a lot of time well
I was the oldest so I was used to being
kind of like that
leadership thing like for my brother and
my little cousin so I didn't have a hard
time stepping away honestly like I
always did my own thing um it was funny
cuz I was like the nerd in high school I
graduated with a four pointer or with a
three .8 from college or the 4.0 so I it
wasn't that hard for me I didn't
need to fit in I guess
to I didn't need that and I it's because
I had so much approval you know from my
house and from just my parents that I
didn't need to be the cool child I guess
so total opposite total opposite so I
really didn't have to um I mean I did go
through a challenging phase of my life I
think when I moved to Florida honestly
is when I went through more of a
challenging face because I was more of
my on my own at that point um we went
through
like um I want to say about two months
where I didn't speak to my mom because
she just wasn't excited about the
decisions I had been making in my life
let's talk about that what were the
decisions so that's where I think um
where there was a little bit of a lot of
um time that I had by myself without
having her there you know I still had my
dad that was talking to me and that
little phase that's where I think was my
roughest time like it was like Ramen
noodle diet time and working tons of
hours a day at the
airport and that was like now I take I
say this term a lot you create your
reality and it comes from I think a lot
of thinking back of that and I grew up
in a very strict religion and so you
know that was the guideline so it was
like a blessing and a curse it was the
blessing because all of my morals came
from there and you know that's where I
think I got a lot of things like love
like I love I wear my heart on my sleeve
so thanks to that but she wasn't happy
you know with the decisions that had I I
decided I it wasn't for me I decided
that I wanted to live my life the way I
felt was right so wow I didn't have a
problem fitting in as a
kid I guess I didn't have that but my
little tough time was when I moved to
Florida so and what I'm what I'm what
I'm hearing here is that you know
because you you've had a great
upbringing you've had great structure
but you becoming a woman and making
decisions on your
own um kind of changed the dynamic of
your relationship with your parents but
also allowed you to become yourself
because when you you know it's great to
have great parents that are very active
and you know involved in our lives Etc
but you know sometimes when you're in
especially when you're in controlled
environments and I I don't I'm not
saying that you you were in a controlled
environment but from what it sounds like
that you know and and and especially
when you're growing up in a religious
environment as well you know the parents
have a they got a
forecast for how they want your life to
be and where where they want you to go
and um and then you
meet the guy that set his house on
fire imagine that well he was a couple
years later after that I by then I had
already my mom and I had were getting
along great she she realized where I was
coming from kind of realized she didn't
100% understand my mindset at that point
but we were fine but yes then came
Lewis when I was how old was I 27 I came
on the scene yeah and then I met him wow
what we'll get into that in a second so
uh leis now um I too kind of grew up in
in a you know I I grew up in a really
negative environment a lot of things
happening my mom in my like I was born a
um and I hate to say it but you know my
mom said she was raped and I was
born um out of that circumstance so I
was born in an abusive environment and
my parents split because of me so there
was a lot of
resentment happening
with me in the home and I wasn't treated
fairly and and you know I always felt
like I was uh you know I was the product
or the cause of things just happening
the way that they are you know with you
going through all of that um you know
with all the the different events that
happened in your
childhood how did you learn to forgive
yourself because children internalize
you know because we love our parents we
love our family but how did you as a
man like forgive yourself for the things
that happened to you you know as a
child man I'll be honest I didn't start
forgiving myself or anyone until last
year really you know um we've been on a
personal development Journey for about
five years and that was thanks to the
woman that's sitting next to me right
now and it was network marketing as how
you know that may sound cliche or you
know funny but it was network marketing
because I I didn't come from a religious
background like my parents he didn't re
you know he didn't really keep an eye on
us too much I was at 14 hanging out with
25 year old gangsters and 30 year old
men you know what I mean like all kinds
of trouble and I never heard a personal
development or or any of that type of
stuff so I think when I started um
it really really started during my you
know Spiritual Awakening as what some
people would call it where I I was just
tired of being the old me you know I
have done all this personal development
where basically they just brainwash you
to believe that you can do anything and
that's where I'm at right now and during
that process you have to shed those
layers of you know um you hating certain
people you not wanting to forgive
certain people like I called my mother
last year for the first time in my life
I've never spoken to my mother the only
time I talked to her I never talked to
her it was I was 18 she sent me a letter
you know and in about halfway down the
letter she asked me for money and I like
whoa I like talk about not wanting to
ever forgive someone that's where I was
at with her at that moment and
thankfully you know
all this personal development and all
this stuff and you know you you you have
to learn to forgive you have to get your
power back you know I think I think
that's very very very very important
like people don't do that they they they
hold on to you know stupid little pissy
fights and and all these little all
these little like the the smallest
tiniest problems you know and they make
it they make them huge and they hold
resentment and then they don't talk to
their family MERS their mom their dadad
brothers and sisters and all this stuff
and it's like really like if that person
was on their deathbed you would be all
over you know you know calling them and
and going to the hospital and all that
like why does it have to wait till then
so with this personal development I was
like okay I have to call my mom I have
to call the people that I hate I
remember one time last year I was in a
um I do um float tanks it's a
deprivation tank and you know I went in
the tank and and and for whatever reason
like every person that I thought to
myself at that moment that I've ever did
wrong that I ever you know like I used
to do crazy stuff man like I we'll talk
about that later but everything bad that
I could remember in that float tank like
I asked for forgiveness and I was like
you know forgive me you know and and I
forgived everyone that I felt that did
me wrong that some you know and we just
have to get through that I think it's
important as the human species like the
human being has to involve and you have
to go through stuff like that man now uh
I'm going to share a little bit of
something about myself um when I was 17
years old I was uh almost uh I was
almost going to go to jail now um
because I was a young kid and hanging
out with the wrong crowd and um you know
you know we did stuff that we shouldn't
have done and um was like this close but
I had good legal team Etc that that that
helped me during that time and also the
people that were accusing me of whatever
they lied so it didn't didn't happen um
that my mentors I met my mentors through
that process and they came in and they
kind of changed my life and you know the
Ryan Perez that people know now they
wouldn't even even guessed that I was in
a different mindset now
um that being said I'm smart enough to
know that there's always a pinnacle in
someone's life when they're going from a
ju to position from hanging out with
gangsters and then starting a new life
and personal development because that's
exactly what I did I was afraid to go
out I was depressed I was smoking too
much weed so I was like in my thoughts I
was afraid to even step out because I
knew I wanted to
change but and I was depressed too I
didn't know what to do with myself I was
parano paranoid and through that process
it kind of I you know then I start
reading thinking Grow Rich and all the
other things to get me to the point
where I am today so I say this all to
say what was your Pinnacle because you
left that out you said hey I was hanging
out with gangsters and personal
development that's like mixing water and
and and oil what was your what was that
Pinnacle that caused you to make that
transition I would say the first big
moment of change would be my first
daughter being born you know um I had
been through relationships where I had
girlfriends with other kids from
different men I had well at one time
kind of like my high school sweetheart
um got pregnant from another guy that I
was almost going to take care of the
baby type of stuff um and then I got
into a
relationship with a with a lady and we
had a kid you know U my first daughter
and you know H having just seeing her
born and stuff I was like man I gotta
change I got to do something you know
different and stuff like that
unfortunately that relationship didn't
go um the way I wanted to and I think a
lot of the things the reasons why they
didn't go the way I wanted to just
because of the my past my childhood I
wasn't ready for a relationship she
wasn't the right one woman I wasn't
ready to have a kid I you know I was
young I was only 22 I mean I didn't know
crap about crap you
know and then um man that relationship
got really really sour I mean you know I
she I got arrested because of that that
relationship I got locked up on a
domestic violence charge where um I
locked her out of the house because she
was hidden me and and all kinds of stuff
and she took a shovel and broke my uh
window and my neighbor called the cops
and on a domestic violence they always
have to take someone to jail so they
took me so here I am in in jail with 72
other guys okay all locked up for the
same reason I remember this guy Sean
Williams I'll never forget this guy he
was locked up seven times from the seven
from the same woman and I was like holy
crap is this what my life is g to be
like with this woman and I said at that
moment right there first I knew I wasn't
going to go back and second I was like
like God there's a God out there
please I was like just send me a one me
that would cherish me respect me that
treat me like a man and I will live
happy happily ever after and behold God
does answer your prayers he answered my
prayers I met Sandra I mean a few months
after that eight or nine months we had
met before that but we didn't establish
a friendship till after exactly and um
man when Sandra came into my life guys I
mean I was
in I was in the dumps I was very
depressed I was about I was weighing
like 180 pounds when Sandra met me like
if I show you a picture okay you would
think like I was from Ethiopia or
something like I was anorexic like I was
depressed stressed out I mean oh my God
go and then Sandra comes into my life
and I just see how she is with her
friends that's the F like guys all my
guys out there let me talk to you for a
second you get with a woman okay and she
doesn't respect herself she doesn't
respect her company she doesn't respect
her family
run okay I'm I'm telling you that right
now fights in the family that's not
normal you know my ex she used to have
fist fights with her mom you know she's
been arrested multiple times having
fights fist fights with her mom her dad
you know all kinds of crazy stuff that
[ __ ] is not normal you know so when
Sandra stepped into the scene she
stepped into my life I saw the total
opposite you know and I was I was at a
crossroad I was like do I stay with the
woman that gave birth to my first
daughter okay or do I go with a woman
that I know cares about me loves me he's
going to give me what I need and I don't
know man I call myself a genius but good
God I was a genius that day I decided to
go with I don't mean to interrupt you
but how did you guys meet because you
guys seem like you know obviously you
guys came from different paths but how
did you guys bump into each other we we
met because a mutual friend a mutual
friend he was a rapper and um we went
out to his one of his shows to support
him and that was the first time I saw
her but all her friends was saying you
know that guy's he's he's he's with
crazy you don't want him he's with crazy
and crazy was my ex yeah you know I was
like oh I don't want
crazy so when we met it literally was
just hey this is so and so and this is
so and so and our mutual friends we had
met because I worked at the airport the
Orlando Airport for a little bit and he
did too so that's how we had that Mutual
it was another couple that's how we had
the mutual friends and and so literally
when we met it was nothing it was just
the oh hey I didn't even know his name
actually um she thought my name was wild
yeah I thought his name was W because
that's what our mutual friend introduced
him as and I was just like okay at the
time it was I was very independent I
hadn't been in a relationship for a
while I was literally doing me I was
like traveling every month um it was
just I was I was loving life and so when
I met him it was nothing it was just a
it was February I won't forget that
because that's when now our second our
second child was born that's it was
right around that time and then the
first time we hung out was I think a
week after you got out of jail right
yeah went downtown we went downtown and
that's when we kind of more got to know
each
and then um and then we it was about a
couple weeks that we kind of talked for
a little bit and then he did the
big it's not you it's me and I said oh
heck no he's going back to
crazy wow I decided huh go ahead oh hold
on one second okay so it's like all
these different things happen all at the
same time now he came out of jail and
you're ant is say beep beep beep stay
away from this guy stay away from this
guy oh you didn't know okay okay okay so
and then did you find out later did you
find out in you know like wait later
later later or did you like within a
week I think right he had told me and I
was like oh okay so I did I was like
okay let me keep my eyes open with this
situation
and um and sure enough that's when
he he told me he wasn't going to try to
work things out with his ex but I'm not
stupid I was like oh no I'm not dumb you
know and his and let's talk about that
okay
so I knew you know the person she was
and I knew what the person my ex was
right and my
dilemma there for a short period of time
was the fact that I did not grow up with
my mom and my dad in the same household
yeah and one of my
biggest reasonings for going back with
my ex was I didn't want that from for my
kids and I think this is another thing
I'm gonna point out to all my guys
listening out there don't do that like
do do not sacrifice your
happiness um you know your kids
happiness you know don't don't sacrifice
those thing like you know going back to
your ex and all this if you know it's a
it's it's not going to work it's an ugly
situation she's crazy she's crazy guys
you know if they've proven themselves
crazy don't do it because every single
time I see that unfold like with my
other friends it never goes anywhere
positive it always
backfires it it it just like it was for
me so what happened I went back to my ex
right Within
a week or two you know she started you
know finding all these messages from
Sandra and all you know all this stuff
and and and and it was just it was just
crazy you know she was breaking my
phones breaking my stuff I didn't know
all this like she was she was being her
she was the same exact person she was
being her so that's what that's what I'm
telling you
guys out there you know when when you're
with crazy crazy is not going to change
right now uh you know what I mean she's
not going to
change so wow now
Sandra what did your what did your
parents think and you know with and then
we're gonna jump into uh CU wow it's
been an hour already um oh wowow yeah so
we're we'll we'll go as long as we need
uh but you know what did your parents
thing how did you you know because you
know here's rainbows and now Rainbow's
in the hood you know what I'm
saying but you know I I don't mean to
I'm not I wasn't to hood I was two Hood
I I was you know at the time I dress
sophisticated I used to wear my dress
shoes know they didn't know I um I was
very
like I was very
careful with who I brought around and
who I let into my life so as soon as he
gave that little he didn't tell me but
I'm not stupid so as soon as he gave
that little bit
of that little bit of like that he's
that I knew I just knew it I'm a woman I
have an intuition and so I immediately I
mean some might even call this drastic
but I was like oh I'm changing my phone
number she cut me off I literally cut
him off cut me off like and he emailed
me and we actually were reading these
emails about a month ago while we were
on the road I was like let's see if we
can find these emails make sure you
erase those
guys so we were looking at the email he
was emailing me for the two months that
he went back over there you know and
tried to work things out and you know I
I was fine it's not like it was a big
thing at the time I was just like okay
well I don't want crazy around my life I
have my apartment I'm on my own my
parents didn't know um I wasn't living
with my parents I was on my own I was 27
I
was 27 26 I don't remember anymore and
um yeah so they they didn't know so they
didn't meet him until it was
serious okay so that now you guys are
you know and obviously you guys found a
connection and you know and and and if
there's anybody that I can feel the love
you know is you guys you know every time
I see you guys' videos you guys mesh so
well uh going through your footage when
we were doing the production and just
seeing how well you work together
uh I think that's amazing I think that
that um uh that that that's something
that you know you can't really get in a
lot of relationships I know me um you
know I'm dating now but it's really hard
to um to date someone that really truly
understands the entrepreneurial life um
so you know the fact that you guys are
able to mesh together and I didn't mean
to make say the comment that you know
Rainbow's in the hood but you know it's
kind of like it was funny drawing the
drying the Dr the position that you know
here you're like there's two different
people and they find a way to come and
to to create something like a rose out
of concrete you know to create Disney
story man create something beautiful so
now the next question is uh now let's
fast forward a bit you had kids Etc when
did you guys decide to start doing
business tell us a little bit about the
um uh about how you guys got into
business and then how you got to where
you are now
okay so when I met Sandra I had I owned
a store downtown Orlando okay it was a
flooring store um and I've always been
self-employed since I was about 18 years
old and I started kind of um in flooring
and stuff So eventually I worked my way
up to having my own
store and she met me there and at the
time I mean there was no Facebook
Instagram or anything like this I was um
I was running the business I was
installing the floors I was making sales
I was posting on Craigslist you know
marketing I was doing what I'm doing now
it's so funny um on on on um on
Craigslist and stuff
and I always say this if if I would have
met Sandra a year before I had started
that we that would have been probably
one of the most successful business
businesses um I didn't last very long
there I was there for a year um I didn't
had no Walkin traffic um flooring is
like the mafia you know once you figure
out things you know once you start
working on big businesses it's like the
bigger jobs you do the less money you
make you know there's all kinds of
things that um we can get into there but
so I had this Florence store after we
met about eight months I got rid of the
Florence store because it was too much
overhead so then um you know we started
looking for contracts I end up finding a
contract for the city it was like a
fiveyear contract um cleaning the bus
stops so we went into business doing
that meanwhile Sandra got into a network
marketing company and um you know we did
she did that for about four years but
yeah so I'm gonna go back a tiny bit so
I was um so he did that and then I was
running like books and all that for that
um that was a lot of
fun putting that together coming we had
to like reorganize all that and then I
was doing my own thing I was actually an
esthetician so I was um and I like that
was a complete startup the place that I
did it at they didn't have no skin care
I like literally had to start with zero
clients work my way up and um shout out
to my clients some of you will probably
see shout out to the room and shout out
to The Salt Room
in though and so my business he was
doing his and then I
was kind of running the book sell and
then I got into network
marketing so I think that's when we
really decided not right away it was me
on my own for quite a bit until for a
long bit yeah for a long bit until I
brought money in the house withw
marketing so for all those ladies out
there that your guys not supporting you
because we did have arguments absolutely
and yeah and we had it was like e Mania
around the house it was crazy he didn't
get it you know why I was investing so
much time no personal development he
didn't have yeah no personal development
at the time so he was seeing me grow
basically and he was it and he was not
having it he was not I mean multiple
times we have arguments like every woman
that's out there I mean men they could
have the same thing you know like like
you were just saying you know you're
dating now and it's hard to find a
person that understands the
entrepreneurial mindset you're
absolutely correct because on this
journey you're you're going to get
knocked down you know what I mean you
you might be somewhere where you're
making a lot of money and then boom you
lose money and and you lose all of it
you get stripped down to nothing that
entrepreneurial mindset is going to be
like okay I start all over I did it once
I could do it again and I think that's
what people don't get they don't if
you're not an entrepreneur if you've
never done a business if you never work
your own business or anything like that
you're not going to understand how we
think straight up
now I I we're we're running out of time
so let's cut into when um when you guys
packed everything up you you now have a
successful business and then you packed
it all up to go rving now I'll tell
you me my name is Ryan Perez and I'm not
into camping I'm not into walking
anywhere I'm a city guy you know I'm
from the Caribbean so you know my family
we are not if we were camping we're
bringing the house with us now um you
know obviously you brought your house
with you but what would possess you to
get an RV pack it all up and start
moving along unplug out of the
Matrix you feel me basically we didn't
want to do what everybody was telling us
to do yeah that [ __ ] got old they were
like you got to get a house you have
kids and you have to go find somewhere
and we could not figure out where the
heck we wanted to set our roots for our
kids and and me so I was actually born
in Colombia I grew up in New York City
and then we lived in Pennsylvania and
then I moved to Florida so I've done a
lot of moving and I love traveling like
I'm obsessed with traveling I've gone
you know I've traveled my whole life and
I've never he never has but what
happened is we literally went on a
weekend trip with his family they had
just gotten an RV we've never owned an
RV we didn't know nothing about it and I
was already making money from my laptop
so that weekend I remember I had a few
webinars I had some stuff to do but I
was able to work while we were away in
the RV and we were like man can you can
you picture living like this so and
choosing our backyard every day he's
like yeah and I was like me too and
literally that week we Dove right in
like so we are we were that crazy
and we were that much on the same page
we literally just jumped right and and
sold everything had seven yard sales had
seven yard sales got rid of all of our
junk we made so much money on that junk
too let me tell you and we hit the road
literally that's how we did it and and
you know what I our
business we only had one income so
that's something that we teach people
now from our own experi experience I
mean the beginning of our RV Journey was
like the first two months we're like yes
and then all of a sudden our income
started crumbling very quick which was
very scary um I mean it was bad we it
was bad and so at that point we had to
make a decision and so thankfully
because of those lessons we now have
seven streams of income coming in so we
don't have to worry about that crazy
mess um so this past year 2017 has been
incredible it's one we've branded us in
our crazy lifestyle and now that's why
we really
want through what we do like there's a
lot of people out there like you like
they're not into camping and and you
know we call it more glamping we have
our house on Wheels with us and we
literally just want to inspire people to
realize that they don't need all the
junk that they have you know they don't
need to carry all that weight on their
shoulders they're of everyday stress
they need to get out in
nature and breathe that good ass Prana
baby yes and get out there and and
figure out their own definition of
freedom you probably hear my
two-year-old right
now yeah I have kids I
understand don't you don't have to worry
about it we're
good okay there she
is okay yeah so we travel now full time
with a two-year-old and 5-year-old
making is way more adventurous yeah we
did a three mile a three mile hike today
on a mountain I know God should be
passed out but
anyways yeah well you know so well
that's that's great and I mean again you
guys don't to worry about the kids I
understand I had a two-year-old once and
uh you know all kind and yeah once well
cuz he's no longer two years old but you
know he was he was uh you just pretty
adventurous and you're talking to
clients and stuff and he wants to go
potty or what doing a live video and you
know they want to come out and open the
refrigerator yeah normal but okay so um
now that you guys have um what are some
parting words about your business before
we get into our second line of
questioning um what do you guys want to
know about first class uh what do you
want everyone to know about first class
RV Adventures
well my name is lwis what was the
question I'm s you said what you want to
know about first class oh I'm sorry and
I'm Sandra and we're with first class RV
Adventures where we support your dreams
it doesn't matter what you want to do
how you want to do it find your
definition of a freedom whatever that is
whether it's living off your laptop and
traveling around the world becoming a
digital Nomad jumping in RV uh traveling
the world whatever you want to do
whatever it is
be you do it make it happen don't be a
carbon copy you are special no one has
your fingerprints you're the only one in
the world with your fingerprints you are
special okay don't be a carbon copy baby
yeah that's our biggest thing awesome
now our second line of questioning um
but folks uh please if you guys haven't
you know like this is why people like
the hustle Zone because people share oh
all kinds of things with me you know and
and that's why that's why we do what we
do um and you know so all the people
that want to be a part of the show I
probably had it so this question so many
times today even from our guests they're
like what topic are we talking about the
topic is you we're talking about
you and
so make sure that when you guys are
signing up to the the entrepreneurs that
you understand we're going to talk about
your life we want to talk about you we
don't want all the fluff and I I again I
want to thank the guests for you know
just divulging so much information
letting us all know what kind of people
that they are so that we can better
support their dreams you know because
they're supporting our dreams we want to
support theirs but always sometimes it's
always nice to have the background story
um for us to fall in love um with the
movement and for us to learn because
again I would love my son to see
something like this because he's going
to learn to be a better person just by
listening to the trials and tribulations
the beauty the the the rainbows the
unicorns all that because it's all
important in making great families and
great making great businesses so we're
going to go on our second line of
questioning here and then we're going to
end the show um so this is the you know
what we call the lightning
round and uh so the lightning round with
ran Perez
okay so I'll start with you Sandra
what's your favorite
dessert oh
Louis
cheesecake that was too easy that was to
Cheesecake uh
leis Sandra's flang oh yeah what is
that it's a Spanish custard okay I was
like Sandra's why I'm like I didn't hear
like
[Laughter]
whoa y you're from the Caribbean bro you
don't know what a FL is no I don't um
but well my parents are from the
Caribbean I have to just uh and then um
uh Monica who is uh she's the queen of
the hustle Zone uh she uh she said yes
flan okay awesome um
so the next question Michael so Sandra
Michael Jackson or
Prince Michael
Jackson okay you guys froze there can
you say that one more time Michael
Jackson and definitely and
leis Michael baby all day awesome now um
what leis what would you tell your
5-year-old
self boy you better strap on it's going
to be a hell of a
ride you ain't
ready uh and facts and Sandra what would
you tell your five-year-old self can I
expand on that sure can I expand on that
yeah I would
say be
careful on what you're scared
of H
[Music]
that's
deep
Law of Attraction baby yeah yeah for
sure uh that was good so Sandra what
would you tell your five-year-old
self to keep loving and keep wearing my
heart on my sleeve don't ever change
that
um leis what is one thing that you would
would change from your past if you had
one thing to change but would what would
that
be if I could change it yeah one part
because everyone will say oh I can't I
don't want to change anything but
there's some things I would change that
would be I change the zeros in my bank
account when I was younger you know I
would
say I would say um save more
money s save way more money oh jeez
I know it's lightning round but what
would I
change I have an
idea all eyes on
me all eyes on me I would have done this
RV thing
sooner can I get an amen from the
congregation
yes she said to get in the
RV reach on the hone I need to get some
organs in here man I gotta get some for
real oh yeah
but
Hallelujah
uh in the
future what Legacy do you want to set
aside for your kids
go
first I want them to be able to do
whatever they
want like as far as who they want to be
who they want to become you know what
extracurricular activities they want to
take part
in I want I want them to be able to to
have those experiences because through
our
experiences is how we grow into an adult
and and and and just pass on all our
love and and all that to
people Sandra so
Legacy Legacy as far as like how he
answered it or Legacy as far as just the
future what would you want to leave for
your kids like what kind of Legacy what
what would you leave behind for people
to know about you
man just like that's hard one that is a
hard one like how to have always have
that adventur
spirit and not to follow the crowd to
really follow their their intuition and
and understand that it's all about it
all stems from selflove I really want
them to love themselves so much that it
just pouring out onto other people
because I think that's kind of what
happened in my case oops sorry I think
that's kind of what happened in my case
was I I was so full of love from all the
love I received and so I want to keep
passing that and I want them to keep
passing that that way it could pour on
to people like I was able to to him
awesome now uh so folks we're going to
conclude the night uh thank thank you
guys for for coming in and sharing your
stories I don't know this if this was
what you expected from the hustle Zone
but did you guys like the did you guys
like the
experience abely this is awesome we love
we love the hustle Zone and bothside
created man I mean you you've made a
brilliant Exquisite platform I mean
that's why I've enjoyed you when I when
when I first friend requested you you
know I was like wow this guy's on to
something he has you know extremely uh
uh sharp Vision like he he
knows he knows where his brand is going
guys you know what I mean and and when
you get behind someone that has that
vision and they do not give up that's a
winner you know that you could bet on
him every single day you know and that's
why I got behind Ryan Perez I mean he
he's if you talk to this guy on the
phone man you will understand he knows
what the he's talking about man you know
he knows and I I appreciate you Ryan I
appreciate what you do I appreciate the
content the value you're giving to
people out there and and giving us the
opportunity and the ability to share our
story on your platform man I appreciate
that so much means a lot brother oh yeah
and it same same thing you guys are you
know the model couple that people should
model themselves after and I'm sure you
guys argue wow I'm sure you guys thank
you I'm sure that we you guys have the
same conversations in every household um
however but you guys really pull it
together to to put on such a great brand
and you know we've yes we've talked on
the phone we've had several
conversations and and it's always great
to see the progression and and you guys
have really transformed your brand um
into something that is is is crazy and
how like LS and I start talking because
like I had a live and I wasn't not
talking to nobody and he was like don't
you engage people on here I'm like have
you ever seen my show
but you know I was here I'm right like
you know the Caribbean and me like you
know I was like going to cuss some
people out
today but no it was it was about to pull
Hast in my
ass but you know but you know to be
honest with you I you know uh like it I
I feel like an extended family member I
feel like a cousin you know because
that's the way that you make you make me
feel you guys make me feel like I'm a
part of the the extended family um and
and in your lives you guys do and then
you guys brought me on to your show and
I and I also appreciated that um and it
was great it was great to have that you
know family Vibe where two people were
talking and you know just really it was
just very you know it was a nice balance
so thank you guys again so much for uh
coming on to the show and we got one
more tradition on the hustle Zone one
more and uh this is going to rock the
house and normally does um so I want you
guys to scream on the the loudest that
you can and I know you kids are GNA love
this I know that you guys are GNA have
you're gonna have to put the kids back
to sleep but we're going to do a call
and response um I'm going to say welcome
to the and then uh you guys are going to
scream hustle
Zone okay now before we do that now we
had
a uh Lis and I had a conversation about
um killing ideas h
killing the baby killing the baby and I
I and because I'm kind of getting into
this whole feminist thing you know
listening to women's perspectives on
things I'm I they got the power bro I'm
not gonna women have the power
man I'm telling you they do and I'm I'm
I I'm no longer to say kill the babies
but we we do want to like when we have
ideas that don't work or we have
strategies that don't work um you you
you have to get rid of them and move
forward and do something else to keep
the train moving like when we had that
conversation what was your perspective
then and what was your perspective
now so when we had that conversation I
was like I went to Sandra I was like yo
you have to start from scratch you know
I kind of I was kind of like man we have
to start from scratch like we're not we
wasn't telling our story correctly and
that was the problem you know and I
learned that with you you know that we
had to tell the story the right way and
and and and and brand it the right way
that way when someone looks at our brand
they kind of know what we're doing and
and and stuff like that and I never
heard that from anyone before until
until you and then you know now I think
about it and I did kill my baby and that
was my first class art my um uh floors
to ceiling business I'm I mean my
construction business like yo I was I
built that like I never finished high
school I didn't go to college you know
anything I was grossing $125
$150,000 you know in the construction
business doing pressure washing you know
and I did kill my baby so when now I
look at it and I'm like okay I did I did
kill my baby and and I'm building a new
brand and and I'm I'm I want to make
sure that we do tell our story the right
way and thanks to Ryan you know we got
this for that no no no no no wait a
minute the that's the video that you
produced for us bro has gotten more
likes views on our YouTube on our
YouTube I mean comments we had the most
people on a live ever at one time we had
over a hundred people at one point on
that live now thank when you when you're
doing this on L stuff guys you're not
going to do things right every single
time you're going to mess something up I
mean and that's part of the process of
being an entrepreneur you learn and you
tweak you learn and you tweak you Market
if it doesn't work you tweak and you
just keep freaking doing that and
eventually all everything is g to come
together you know and just like when if
you look at our page like we're so
public about our stuff like our lives
you go through our Facebook if you
really want to know who we are guys you
go through our Facebook and everything
we've talked about right here you will
be able to see on our timeline yeah like
you know when we were going to plasma
places to get donations and churches to
get food and all that crap it's all
right there on our Facebook you know so
I want to encourage everyone not to give
up and and get with people collaborate
don't be scared a lot of people would
see Ryan and said oh I can't do what
Ryan does I can't work with Ryan you
know what I mean no don't be I mean if
you look at my stuff I was oh my gosh my
videos were terrible a year a year ago
they're still terrible now you know we
just we learn every single time we do
these man so my perspective now is keep
[ __ ]
going don't stop don't stop and uh wow
that was great and and and again like
you know the whole thing about your
guys' story now I get it and before it
did like you know we had that
conversation because I think place we
were trying to figure out like I don't
know I don't know what the conversation
was but I was like I don't get
it but because there were so many
different things that you wanted to do
you had all these ideas but then all of
a sudden and I'm subscribed to you guys
on YouTube by the way so I do get your
notifications as soon as they go up and
I do watch sh and it you know and it's
about RV and you guys got sponsors out
of the yin-yang you guys got all kinds
of people that are supporting your
vision because everyone knows what
you're all about and you didn't really
change much you just solidified the
story and what we did was lock down into
our Niche because we wasn't but
it really thanks to you because after
that combo that you had with him I
remember he came up to me and I said
start from scratch are you crazy
yeah and I said oh heck no I was like
what this means to me is that he doesn't
understand so we have to figure out how
to make people understand and that thing
that was a perfect conversation you yes
we were able to hone in and and we said
okay we're gonna go all in on our
freaking Niche we don't care explain it
we do a lot of things you know we're in
cryptocurrency Bitcoin all we do a lot
of lot of things
but our Niche is something that both of
us are so happy doing we get so much
excitement doing our videos climbing
mountains and all this stuff we love
that stuff man so it comes just totally
natural to us so folks this is has been
probably the longest hustle Zone that
we've ever had sorry I no but honest
talk along I like in half an hour of the
story I was already determining that
this will probably be the longest
because you guys have such an
interesting you know you will probably
want to get this all in um you know so I
kind of you know I I just kind of let it
go I don't really have a time because
you know with the hustle Zone we kind of
vibe we We Vibe off of uh um
offer right because someone's boring and
they're like well yeah so I sell and uh
that's about it I'm like okay bye but uh
I'm joking I would I would do that but
you know you guys uh you guys are this
was a great interview and you guys are
definitely someone to watch these people
these people are someone that you guys
should follow uh because they are living
their passion every single day of their
lives they're seeing a they have a new
backyard every day and they're sharing
that so that you know if you can't get
better content than that because some
people got the green screens in the
background trying to put like palm trees
and here these guys are you know driving
around
so uh we got to close out this show
before I get old and I start like hey
like we're gonna do this we got do the
thing so okay
so the call and response so I'm gonna
say welcome to the and I need you guys
to scream as loud as you can scream
hustles on okay so welcome to the
[Music]
that that that was crazy we were
clipping out over here like God damn
that was great that was great thank you
guys so much baby so if you guys can
just hang tight um I'm just gonna close
out the show here uh so yeah
folks so
folks they can't hear you leis but you
know I remember your
name but
uh uh
the one thing about LS is that his laugh
right gets it's so contagious um so I I
can't even put him on mute right now but
anyway
um folks this is why you guys tune in
because you're going to get these type
of stories heartfelt we say expand the
crop that is our slogan but we're going
to change it because someone a famous
person actually was like expand the crap
oh I like it you know I like this idea
I'm like no it's not crap it's crop um
so uh so we're going to change it into
we have we just started the more
campaign um you know so you'll notice
that there's a plus sign in all of our
logos because we're talking about
narratives we're talking about branding
this is what we do for a living and that
plus sign removes the zero out of hustle
Zone and removes the zero of or the O
out of bow tie because zero is not a
variable it's a decision it's a choice
the plus means more means it is a
variable and if you turn it 45° you get
an X which also stands for a variable so
both are creative you do more you
achieve more you get more so we are
starting the more campaign we started
three we have three companies now we're
talking about multiple streams of income
we have B creative which is The Branding
agency we build online businesses we got
hustle Zone we see more we hear more um
and then we have The Branding gym where
we get more because we do now unlimited
graphic design so to help you tell your
story better we have an unlimited
graphic design team that will you know
create all kinds of things for you uh
for a nominal price of 300 or sorry 400
$ per month and it is topof thee line
graphic design Services um and then with
B creative we build online businesses
and our websites do more uh we have crms
we have all kinds of things that are
hooked up to the website so that when
you have a great live like this and you
have a website you go to the website and
the website now acts as the business and
it takes in the leads and then you could
take payments on your website all kinds
of things so we're like
Shopify but but we are on steroids like
the type of solutions that we provide
we're we provide a steroid type solution
where you're just getting a full online
business we don't even like to call them
websites because they're literally an
online business you guys want to check
us out go to hustlez own.tv or bolti
creative.com or branding jim.com and
you're going to see this our narrative
our brand narrative through that so
thank you guys folks for tuning in to
the hustle Zone and there's going to be
more where that came from and remember
remember we are the world's first living
documentary right we are documenting
entrepreneurs lives from timbuk 2 from
Arizona all the way to Canada and we're
going to be hitting all over the world
and we're going to be starting a
$100,000 campaign because we want to
travel just like first class RV and we
want to interview entrepreneurs from all
over the world and we want to document
the story and build this website into
something that you've never seen before
so $100,000 Campaign which will be
launching soon so thank you guys folks
for coming into the hustle Zone and I'll
talk to you guys later